jobsatm.com 2014-12-22

# Privacy Policy | JobsATM.com

Privacy Policy

Jobsatm.com always committed to protecting Your privacy as it is very important. We understand that you need to be in control of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains the manner in which we collect personal information from you and the purpose for that collection. This Privacy Policy is designed to ensure that you are aware of how your personal information is being used and to provide you with choices about that use. By visiting the Site or submitting your personal information, you accept the terms described in this Privacy Policy.  
Collection of Personal Information

To establish a brand of trust and quality by offering a better, quality Business Promotional media to our clients and a regularly updated Quality and reliable set of Listings for our readers in the Internet arena and become one of the most popular and sought after portals in the Online Marketing Space.

Full Name  
Email address  
Mobile phone number  
Postal address / Code  
Demographic information (like your age, gender, occupation, professional experience, education, etc.);  
Preferences and interests (such as newspapers read and so on);  
Financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and  
Other Information , which is required to buy product/service

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.  
Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings.

A browser cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser to be stored for future use. The data in the browser cookie will be sent back to the web server whenever the browser reconnects to the web site. Cookies are commonly used to store user preference information, such as web site options. Cookies are also used to store shopping cart contents. The most security-relevant use of browser cookies is when they are used to store authentication data, such as user names and passwords. Third-Party Ad networks will collect the information to process your requirements.

HOW YOU CAN CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us via web form /email.
